fathomevents.com 2017-02-09

# Privacy | Fathom Events

## FATHOM EVENTS’ PRIVACY POLICY

**Effective Date: August 11, 2016**

AC JV, LLC ( **"Fathom," “Us,”** or **“We”** ) is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of Fathom’s websites and mobile applications including www.fathomevents.com, corporate.fathomevents.com and m.fathomevents.com, (these web sites and mobile applications and the services provided or offered through these web sites and mobile applications, whether existing now or in the future, collectively referred to as the **“Sites”** and individually referred to as the **“Site”** ).

This privacy policy (the **“Policy”** ) tells you how we collect, use and share information we collect on our Sites effective as of the date posted above.  By using the Sites and submitting information you agree that we may use and disclose your information according to the terms of this Policy. 

Amendments to this Policy will be posted on the Sites and will be effective when posted.  Your continued use of any of the Sites following the posting of any amendment will constitute your acceptance of that amendment, except if your personally identifiable information will be used in a materially different manner.  See the Notification of Changes section below for further information. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, you should contact Fathom by e-mail at [info@fathomevents.com](mailto:info@fathomevents.com).

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

**1.2 INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE.**

We may collect information that identifies you personally ( **“Personally identifiable information”** ) that you provide as you access and use the Sites and other information that may not identify you personally ( **“aggregated information”** ).   

We may collect personally identifiable information from you through a number of voluntary sources on the Sites, such as responses, registrations, reviews, comments, emails, postings, photographs, messages, the interfacing with social networking sites or other electronic submissions and communications sent by you to Fathom or the Sites. We may also collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to submit information on our Careers page, you enroll in our Stay Connected service, or join our SMS service.  We may require certain location information such as ZIP Code in order to provide information that you request, such as venues close to you.

Registration is not mandatory to access the public areas of the Sites.  Registration may, however, be required for access to certain areas of the Sites and the products and services provided through those areas of the Sites.  The areas of the Sites that may require registration are noted on each Site. If you choose to register we may collect your name, contact information such as phone number, address and email address. Registered users select a username and password to be used to access their account and the portions of that Site available to account holders.

The personally identifiable information we may collect from you may include, by way of example: 

  * Domain name and IP address;
  * E-mail address;
  * Contact information (including, name, address, zip code, country, and phone number);
  * Age;
  * Gender;
  * Marital status;
  * Occupation and position;
  * Employer and employment history;
  * Income information;
  * Financial information, such as account or credit card numbers;
  * Mobile phone number, mobile carrier's name, unique identifier for a mobile device and the date, time and content of mobile communications with Fathom;
  * GPS or other location-based or geo-positioning information (if we have your permission);
  * Audit Information;
  * User-specific and aggregate information on areas of the Sites accessed;
  * Username and password information for each Site; and
  * Other information volunteered by You, such as information provided through responses, registrations, reviews, comments, emails, postings, photographs, messages, the interfacing with social networking sites (such as a profile photo, birthday and status), or other electronic submissions and communications sent by you to Fathom or the Sites.

The Sites may have features that allow you to store and share your information or content with others.  The Sites may include features and functions that allow you to post and share content, messages and reviews to forums, message boards, chat rooms or bulletin boards.  We may record and store archives of these communications and content on our servers.  You acknowledge and consent to the recording and storage of such communications and content.  If you choose to provide personally identifiable information through use of these features, that information may be available to a wider community and individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge.  We recommend that you think carefully about sharing this type of information, including through forums, message boards, chat rooms or bulletin boards.

Information that you post to any of the Sites as comments, reviews, content, tweets, etc. will be visible to the general public.  We may show posts from our social media accounts on our websites.  YOU SHOULD NOT SUBMIT OR POST ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANY OF THE SITES UNLESS YOU WANT THAT INFORMATION TO BE ACCESSIBLE BY OTHER USERS OF THE SITES. 

We may also provide you with the ability to create a personal profile on a Site containing personally identifiable information provided by you and to make your personal profile available to other users of the Sites.  You may adjust the scope and nature of the information you make available to other users of the Sites through Your personal profile as indicated on the Sites.  YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY INFORMATION INCLUDED IN YOUR PERSONAL PROFILE AND SHARED WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITES.  YOU SHOULD NOT CREATE A PERSONAL PROFILE UNLESS YOU WANT TO SHARE YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITES.

The personally identifiable information that Fathom collects from users of the Sites may be used for our general commercial purposes, for example to grow our business, to provide the services and products offered through the Site, to customize advertising and other content displayed on the Site and/or the layout of the Site for each individual user of the Site, to notify users of the Site about updates to and activities on the Site and about goods and services that we feel may be of interest to you, to improve the content of the Site, to analyze data and patterns regarding usage of the Site, to contact users of the Site for marketing purposes, and to contact users of the Site for information verification purposes.  We may use information you submit through the Careers page to evaluate and make employment decisions.

We may use your contact information, on occasion, send out service related announcements.  For instance, if our Sites or any of the services offered through the Sites are temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. 

We may send new registrants of the Sites a welcoming email to verify password and username.  Established members may occasionally also receive information on products, services and special deals, and periodic newsletters.  Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.  Please see the Choice and Opt-out section.

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and with regard to issues relating to their account, we reply via email, in accordance with the users' wishes. 

**1.2 INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY**

We may automatically collect personally identifiable information from you when you access the Sites.  Where possible, our server automatically recognizes each visitor’s Internet Protocol addresses.  We also collect information about how visitors use the Sites (for example what pages are viewed and products and services are purchased).  This information allows us to improve the content of the Sites and facilitate market research.  Sometimes, we utilize the services of a third party to help us understand this information better, although the information that is disclosed to these entities remains at all times in anonymous and non-personally identifiable form.  . 

**1.3   ENHANCEMENT OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. **

We may combine and enhance our user database information with third party data and information to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers in which we think our users would be interested.  Certain summary demographics are also used in our research product offerings.  Individual personally identifiable information is never used in our research product offering and is never tied back to an individual user or resold for any purposes.  

**2\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We may reveal information about you to unaffiliated third parties: (1) if you request or authorize it; (2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) if the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, governmental and quasi-governmental requests, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) if the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) if the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

We may also share certain personally identifiable information we collect through the Sites with third party companies so that they may offer products and services to users of our Sites that we believe will be of interest to those users. We may also share certain personally identifiable information with third party advertisement serving companies to better target the advertising and other content displayed on the Sites and provide pertinent offers we think may be of interest to our users.  In addition, third party advertisers may receive certain personally identifiable information about you if you click on advertisements displayed on the Sites (and clicking on any advertisement displayed on the Sites will be considered your consent to “opt in” for this transfer). 

We may disclose aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics, to our affiliates and third parties for any purpose.

**3\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.**

California law provides that California residents have a right to request that businesses tell them how their personally identifiable information has been shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  However, there is an exception to this requirement for businesses that have adopted and disclosed, in their privacy policy, a policy of not disclosing a person’s personally identifiable information to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes if that person has exercised an option to opt-out of the disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for such purposes.

Fathom has adopted a policy of allowing you to opt-out of the disclosure of your personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes and thus falls within this exception.  Instructions for opting out can be found in the section below entitled “Choice and Opt-Out.” 

**4\. ACCESS, REVIEW, UPDATE.**

The users of the Sites should email us at info@fathomevents.com to review, delete/deactivate and update the personal information that was previously provided to us.

**5\. CHOICE AND OPT-OUT.**

We provide you with a choice whether to receive certain emails.

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes.  If you are a user of the Sites and you no longer wish to receive promotional email, mail, or telephone calls from us or have your email address or postal address shared with third parties, you may opt-out of receiving promotional email, mail or telephone calls from us or having your email address or postal address shared with third parties.  You do not have the opportunity to opt-out of service related or transactional emails or communications about your account; these communications are not promotional in nature.

In addition, if you would prefer that we not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of having your personally identifiable information shared with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

All opt-out requests can be made by emailing us at: info@fathomevents.com or writing us at AC JV, LLC Attn: Customer Service, 5990 Greenwood Plaza Blvd., Building 2, Suite 100, Greenwood Village, CO, 80111.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our Sites. These companies may use personally or non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to the Sites and other web sites or applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative, a coalition of online advertising networks that provides an opportunity for consumers to opt-out of targeted advertising by member companies.  It should be noted that opting out does not mean you will not see advertisements online, but these advertisements will not be targeted based on your online user interest profile.

**6\. CHILDREN.**

The Sites are not directed to children under 13 years of age and the Terms of Use for the Sites specifically prohibits use of the Sites by children under 13 years of age.  Children under 13 may not use or access the Sites under any circumstances.  If you are 13 or older and younger than 18, then you may access and use the Site only if you have your parents' or guardians' prior permission. Fathom does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. 

**7\. COOKIES, PIXELS AND WEB BEACONS.**

**"Cookies"** are commonly used pieces of information in the form of small files that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Sites.  We may use cookies for various purposes, for example to save user preferences, customize content of the Sites for individual users, to ensure that users are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, to record session information, such as items that users add to their shopping cart, to alert users to new areas that might be of interest upon return to the Sites, and to save certain information about users of the Sites and others who visit the Sites, in order to facilitate and enhance interaction with the Sites.  Fathom does not use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to Fathom or the Sites. 

A cookie does not collect or keep your name or other personally identifying information; however, we may link the information obtained through cookies to other personally identifiable information to give us a better understanding of your preferences, so that we can provide a more meaningful experience to you on our Sites. 

We may use third parties, such as an outside advertisement serving company to display advertisements on the Sites.  We may also use a third party provider to analyze data and patterns regarding usage of the Sites and such third party provider may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, tracking agents or any other visitor identification technology to collect such information. These third parties may place and collect cookies when you visit the Sites.  These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website.  We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the third party. 

Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.  Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

**8\. OTHER WEB SITES; LINKS; WIDGETS.**

Certain of the web sites of Fathom’s affiliates, promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party web sites and third-party widgets are accessible through the Sites.  These third party web sites and third-party widgets have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. FATHOM IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ACTIONS OR PRIVACY POLICIES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES.  YOU SHOULD CHECK THE APPLICABLE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THOSE THIRD PARTIES WHEN PROVIDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THROUGH LINKED WEB SITES AND WIDGETS.

**9\. CONSENT TO THE USE OF THIRD PARTY PROVIDERS.**

In addition to the specific third parties noted in this Policy, Fathom may also contract with other third parties to provide various services to Fathom relating to the Sites on an outsourced basis rather than performing the services itself.  For example, Fathom may contract with an email provider to handle the distribution of email messages to members of the Sites.  Likewise, Fathom may contract with a web site hosting provider to host all or a portion of the Sites for Fathom.  Fathom may also contract with third party mobile providers to enable the mobile user services provided through the Sites.  We may also use a third party provider to serve advertisements and collect and analyze data and patterns regarding usage of the Sites.  By visiting the Sites, all visitors consent to Fathom providing both personal and non-personal information received from those visitors to these third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party provider to provide these outsourced services to Fathom.  In addition, all visitors consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their personal and non-personal information by Fathom and these third party providers as follows:

Cookie and Pixel Information: Cookies and pixels provide Fathom and its providers with the ability to create an ID in order for Fathom and its providers to match collected data to an anonymous machine including:

  * The URLs (or website address) of web pages which have been viewed;
  * The date and time of visit to a web page;
  * Whether the user has clicked on an ad of one of our advertisers, visited their website, or undertaken a transaction with them;

Session Information: This information relates to user, campaign and interest-based history and is used for frequency capping and interest targeting. This information is gathered from websites visited and clicks registered by the user’s machine.

Request-based Information: This information is passed to Fathom and its providers by the user’s computer browser with every request and is stored entirely anonymously for statistical purposes only:

  * IP (Internet Protocol) addresses - Every device connected to the Internet has an IP address. This cannot be traced to an individual user but can be used for geographic targeting and statistical measurements;
  * Browser type - e.g. Are you using Microsoft Explorer or Apple’s Safari;
  * Computer Operating System - e.g. Are you using Windows Vista or Apple OS.

Mobile Device Information: This information is passed to Fathom and its providers by the mobile communications with Fathom:

  * Mobile phone number;
  * Mobile carrier's name;
  * Unique identifier for a mobile device;
  * Date, time and content of communication with Fathom; and
  * Geo-location information if provided as part of location serving.

**10\. CONSENT TO THE INTERFACE WITH SOCIAL NETWORKING SITES.**

In order to enhance your experience on the Sites, Fathom may retrieve and collect information about you from your account(s) on various social networking sites, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us, in accordance with the policies and terms of the applicable social networking site.  The information you allow us to access varies by social networking site, and it is affected by the privacy settings you establish with the social networking site.  By accessing or using the Sites in connection with a social networking site(s), you authorize us to collect, store and use in accordance with this Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network site could provide us.  In addition, some social networking sites have features which allow you to send information about your activity on the Sites back to the social networking site (for example, to be published in your profile).  If you choose to use these features, then your activity on the Sites will be shared with the social networking site(s).  Individuals reading this information on social networking site(s) may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. 

**11\. LOCATION SERVING.**

As part of the services offered by the Sites, we may display a map via the Google Maps API. Click here to view Google's Privacy Policy.   If you allow a mobile Site to get your location, we may collect, depending on the capabilities of your mobile device, information about the wifi routers closest to you, cell ids of cell towers, closest to you and the strength of your wifi or cell signal.  While we use this information to return an estimated location, location data may not be accurate.

**12\. INTERNATIONAL USERS.**

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Sites are hosted on computer servers located in the United States.  Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United Sates federal and state governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain access to your information through applicable United States laws.  Your use of a Site or the your submission of any personally identifiable information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information outside of your home country, including the United States, which may have very different date protection and privacy rules and regulations than in your home country.

**13\. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES.**

If we decide to change this Policy, we will post material changes on the Sites or take other steps so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and if we disclose it.  Unless we seek and receive your consent, we will use information in accordance with the Policy under which the information was last collected. Users may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by emailing us at [info@fathomevents.com](mailto:info@fathomevents.com.%C2%A0).

**14\. SECURITY.**

We will use reasonable security measures on the Sites to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information.  For example, our policy is that only those individuals who need your personally identifiable information to perform a specific job are granted access to that personally identifiable information.  Likewise, all employees and contractors are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.  Furthermore, when Fathom transfers and receives certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, it redirects visitors to a secure server.  Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.  While we employ the above steps, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Fathom and you do so at your own risk.

Fathom is not responsible for any loss or misuse of your username and password.  If we receive instructions using your username and password we will consider it authorized by you.  ALWAYS REMEMBER THAT IN ORDER TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY YOU SHOULD NOT SHARE YOUR USERNAME OR PASSWORD WITH OTHERS.

**15\. DO NOT TRACK NOTICE.**

Fathom does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

**16\. CONTACT INFORMATION.**

All inquiries concerning this statement and the Sites in general may be sent to [info@fathomevents.com](mailto:info@fathomevents.com).

**Thank you for visiting the Sites.  **
